{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--0", "prompt": "How many figures are in the paper On the Sentence Embeddings from Pre-trained Language Models?", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "2"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--1", "prompt": "How many tables are in the paper On the Sentence Embeddings from Pre-trained Language Models?", "website": "https://arxiv.org/","type": "golden","ans": "8"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--2", "prompt": "What is the impact factor of 'IEEE Transactions on Neural Networks and Learning Systems'?", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "10.2"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--3", "prompt": "Check if 'GPT-3' is discussed in ' Understanding the Capabilities, Limitations, and Societal Impact of Large Language Models'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "Yes"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--4", "prompt": "How many figures are in 'Safety Implications of Explainable Artificial Intelligence in End-to-End Autonomous Driving'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "13"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--5", "prompt": "Check if the paper 'A Comprehensive Survey on Blockchain Technology and Its Applications' includes a section on 'Smart Contract'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "Yes"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--6", "prompt": "Searching Chinese Benchmark, how many papers announced in December 2023 mention being accepted for AAAI 2024?", "website": "https://arxiv.org/","type": "golden","ans": "2"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--7", "prompt": "When was the paper 'GPT-4 Technical Report' first submitted?", "website": "https://arxiv.org/","type": "golden","ans": "March 15, 2023, at 17:15:04 UTC."}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--8", "prompt": "How many formulas are in the paper 'Dense Passage Retrieval for Open-Domain Question Answering', and which one is the loss function?", "website": "https://arxiv.org/","type": "golden","ans": "2 formulas, the second one is loss function."}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--9", "prompt": "What evaluation metrics are used in the paper 'Generative Adversarial Networks in Computer Vision'?", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "Inception Score, FID"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--10", "prompt": "Check if the paper 'V2X-Real: A Largs-Scale Dataset for Vehicle-to-Everything Cooperative Perception' includes a dataset.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "Yes"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--11", "prompt": "Find the ORCID of the first author in 'Advancements in Photovoltaic Cell Materials: Silicon, Organic, and Perovskite Solar Cells'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "https://orcid.org/0000-0003-4134-3344"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--12", "prompt": "Determine the programming languages used in the implementations discussed in 'Natural Language Processing with Transformers'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "Python"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--13", "prompt": "Find the impact factor of the journal where 'Advancements in Photovoltaic Cell Materials: Silicon, Organic, and Perovskite Solar Cells' was published.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "3.1"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--14", "prompt": "Identify the simulation tools used in the research presented in 'odeling and Simulation of a Fully Autonomous Electric Vehicle (AEV)'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "MATLAB/Simulink"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--15", "prompt": "Determine the ethical considerations mentioned in the paper 'Navigating Ethical Challenges in Business Consulting with Generative AI: Balancing Innovation and Responsibility'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "Bias and Discrimination, Transparency and Accountability, Privacy and Data Protection, Human Oversight and Dependency, Job Displacement and Societal Impact"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--16", "prompt": "Search the title 'GPT-4 Technical Report' and access this paper through HTML format. Read the paper on this page and tell me what is 'one of the main goals of developing such models' mentioned in the Introduction.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "One of the main goals of developing such models is to improve their ability to understand and generate natural language text, particularly in more complex and nuanced scenarios."}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--17", "prompt": "Provide the published conference of the paper 'Exploring Robot Trajectories in Panoramic Vision-Based Control Using Deep Reinforcement Learning'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "2025 IEEE/SICE International Symposium on System Integration (SII)"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--18", "prompt": "Find the publication date of the paper 'Quantum Computing: Circuits, Algorithms, and Applications'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "06 February 2024"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--19", "prompt": "Search the papers in CVPR 2023 with the Best Paper Award.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "'Visual Programming: Compositional Visual Reasoning Without Training' and 'Planning-Oriented Autonomous Driving'."}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--20", "prompt": "Identify the conference where the paper 'Neural architecture optimization' by Renqian Luo et al. was presented.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS) 2018"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--21", "prompt": "Check if the paper titled 'ArtCrafter: Text-Image Aligning Style Transfer via Embedding Reframing' disclose code.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "No"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--22", "prompt": "Check if the paper titled 'Rethink Arbitrary Style Transfer with Transformer and Contrastive Learning' disclose code.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "No"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--23", "prompt": "Which conference accepted the paper titled Reverse Engineering Self-Supervised Learning?", "website": "https://arxiv.org/","type": "golden", "ans": "NeurIPS 2023"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--24", "prompt": "When was the paper titled From Representational Harms to Quality-of-Service Harms: A Case Study on Llama 2 Safety Safeguards first announced?", "website": "https://arxiv.org/","type": "golden", "ans": "March 20, 2024"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--25", "prompt": "Does the paper titled Social Choice Should Guide AI Alignment in Dealing with Diverse Human Feedback include ethics statements?", "website": "https://arxiv.org/","type": "golden", "ans": "Yes"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--26", "prompt": "Check if the paper titled Improving Neural Network Representations Using Human Similarity Constraints using CIFAR-100 dataset.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/","type": "golden", "ans": "Yes"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--27", "prompt": "Check if the paper titled  Revisiting Prompt Pretraining of Vision-Language Models uses the 'ImageNet-21k' dataset.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/","type": "golden", "ans": "Yes"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--28", "prompt": "Please provide the list of authors for the paper titled Barrow Entropy and AdS Black Holes in RPS Thermodynamics.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/","type": "golden", "ans": "Yahya Ladghami, Brahim Asfour, Amine Bouali, Ahmed Errahmani, and Taoufik Ouali."}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--29", "prompt": "Does the paper 'Numerical Evolutions of the Linearised Conformal Einstein Field Equations in the Inversion-Minkowski Spacetime' mention 'Quantum Gravity' in its abstract?", "website": "https://arxiv.org/","type": "golden", "ans": "No"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--30", "prompt": "Does the paper 'Universal quantum computation using Ising anyons from a non-semisimple Topological Quantum Field Theory' with Experimental Validation exist?", "website": "https://arxiv.org/","type": "golden", "ans": "No"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--31", "prompt": "Check if the paper 'Pre-trained models for natural language processing: A survey' discusses a comparison between BERT and GPT.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "Yes"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--32", "prompt": "Check if the paper titled 'Image Synthesis with Adversarial Networks: a Comprehensive Survey and Case Studies' disclose code.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "Yes" }
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--33", "prompt": "Check if the paper titled 'Exploring AI-Enabled Cybersecurity Frameworks: Deep-Learning Techniques, GPU Support, and Future Enhancements' discloses code.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "No" }
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--34", "prompt": "Find the source code link of the paper 'PAGE-Net: Interpretable and Integrative Deep Learning for Survival Analysis Using Histopathological Images and Genomic Data'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "https://github.com/DataX-JieHao/PAGE-Net"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--35", "prompt": "Which machine learning dataset is utilized in the paper 'Enhancing Image Classification with Augmentation: Data Augmentation Techniques for Improved Image Classification'?", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "Caltech-101 dataset" }
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--36", "prompt": "Please provide the number of references cited in the paper 'Deep Reinforcement Learning for Robotics: A Survey of Real-World Successes'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "212" }
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--37", "prompt": "Does paper Fairness And Bias in Artificial Intelligence: A Brief Survey of Sources, Impacts, And Mitigation Strategies discuss 'Bias in Machine Learning Algorithms' and includes a detailed section on fairness considerations?", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "Yes" }
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--38", "prompt": "What is the total number of pages in the paper 'Survey of Large Multimodal Model Datasets, Application Categories and Taxonomy'?", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "19" }
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--39", "prompt": "Does the paper 'Abstractive Text Summarization: State of the Art, Challenges, and Improvements' mention 'BERT' in its abstract?", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "Yes" }
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--40", "prompt": "Which university is affiliated with the authors of the paper titled 'Adapting to the Long Tail: A Meta-Analysis of Transfer Learning Research for Language Understanding Tasks'?", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "Carnegie Mellon University" }
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--41", "prompt": "How many tables are in the paper 'A Comprehensive Survey of Mixture-of-Experts: Algorithms, Theory, and Applications'?", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "0" }
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--42", "prompt": "In the 2022 research paper titled Analyzing EEG Data with Machine and Deep Learning: A Benchmark by Danilo Avola et al., what are the four machine learning models that were used?", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "MLP, CNN, LSTM, and GRU."}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--43", "prompt": "Provide me with the DOI of the paper 'Generating Semantic Maps through Multidimensional Scaling: Linguistic Applications and Theory'?", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans":"10.1515/cllt-2021-0018"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--44", "prompt": "In Table 2 of the 2017 Transformer paper titled 'Attention Is All You Need', which two language pairs were used for translation results?", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans":"English-French and English-German"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--45", "prompt": "Identify the funding agencies acknowledged in the paper 'Nanomaterials for Energy Storage Applications'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "Author JS acknowledge the Department of Science and Technology (DST), New Delhi, and UGC New Delhi for financial support. Author JS also acknowledge to BHU for providing a seed grant under BHU, IoE scheme."}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--46", "prompt": "Determine the number of citations listed in the bibliography of 'Artificial Intelligence in Education: A Review'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "206"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--47", "prompt": "Determine the number of figures included in the paper 'Deep Learning Approaches for Protein Structure Prediction'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "8"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--48", "prompt": "Provide the list of figures in the paper 'Advancements in Speech Recognition: A Systematic Review of Deep Learning Transformer Models, Trends, Innovations, and Future Directions'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "Figure 1: Flowchart of the steps followed to select the articles, Figure 2: Distribution of research per type, Figure 3: Distribution of research by year of publication, Figure 4: Type of dataset distribution for online accessible, Figure 5: Environment conditions, Figure 6: Distribution of various types of evaluations, where 'Type of Evaluation' is on the x-axis and the count is on the y-axis, Figure 7: Distribution of various types of models, where 'Type of model' is on the x-axis and the count is on the y-axis."}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--49", "prompt": "List the keywords associated with the paper 'Machine Learning for Healthcare: Applications and Challenges'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "Machine Learning, Healthcare, Predictive Analytics, Personalized Medicine, Medical Imaging, Ethical Concerns, Data Privacy, Regulatory Oversight, Healthcare Innovation"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--50", "prompt": "How many tables are included in the paper 'A Survey of Deep Learning and Foundation Models for Time Series Forecasting'?", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "8"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--51", "prompt": "What is the total number of pages in 'Neural Architecture Search: A Survey'?", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "21"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--52", "prompt": "List the authors of 'Comparative analysis of intestinal tumor segmentation in PET CT scans using organ based and whole body deep learning'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "Mahsa Torkaman, Skander Jemaa, Jill Fredrickson, Alexandre Fernandez Coimbra, Alex De Crespigny, Richard A. D. Carano "}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--53", "prompt": "Check if 'COVID-19' is mentioned in the abstract of 'Artificial intelligence, ChatGPT, and other large language models for social determinants of health: Current state and future directions'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "Yes"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--54", "prompt": "Identify the journal of 'Adaptive heuristic edge assisted fog computing design for healthcare data optimization'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "Journal of Cloud Computing "}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--55", "prompt": "Does 'A review of Explainable Artificial Intelligence in healthcare' include a section on SHapley Additive exPlanations (SHAP)?", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "No"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--56", "prompt": "List the datasets used in 'Learning to Focus: Cascaded Feature Matching Network for Few-shot Image Recognition'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "Omniglot, miniImageNet"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--57", "prompt": "Check if 'DeepSeek-R1' is referenced in 'A Survey on Evaluation of Large Language Models'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "No"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--58", "prompt": "Identify the publication year for 'Zero-Shot Learning: A Comprehensive Evaluation of the Good, the Bad, and the Ugly'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "2018"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--59", "prompt": "Identify the funding source for the research in 'The changing scenario of drug discovery using AI to deep learning: Recent advancement, success stories, collaborations, and challenges'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "This study was supported by research grants from the Zuoying Armed Forces General Hospital (KAFGH-ZY-A-110011, KAFGH-ZY-A-10901"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--60", "prompt": "List the keywords of 'Edge-Computing-Enabled Smart Cities: A Comprehensive Survey'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "Edge Computing, Smart Cities, Internet of Things, Mobile cloud computing, Cloudnet, Fog computing, Mobile edge computing, Micro Data centers"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--61", "prompt": "What is the DOI of 'Using machine learning for healthcare challenges and opportunities'?", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "10.1016/j.imu.2022.100924"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--62", "prompt": "Who is the corresponding author in 'A review of object detection: Datasets, performance evaluation, architecture, applications and current trends'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "Fan Zhang"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--63", "prompt": "Which university is affiliated with the authors of the paper 'Deep Reinforcement Learning Versus Evolution Strategies: A Comparative Survey'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": " Delft University of Technology"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--64", "prompt": "Identify the journal for 'Zero-Shot Learning: A Comprehensive Evaluation of the Good, the Bad, and the Ugly'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "IEEE Transactions on Pattern Analysis and Machine Intelligence (TPAMI)"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--65", "prompt": "Does 'Blockchain-Based Supply Chain Systems, Interoperability Model in a Pharmaceutical Case Study' include a case study on pharmaceutical tracking?", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "Yes"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--66", "prompt": "List the authors of  'Image recognition: progress, trends and challenges'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "Charles Z. Liu, S. Ramakrishnan"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--67", "prompt": "List the authors of 'The role of robotics in medical science: Advancements, applications, and future directions'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "Arun Agarwal, Rishi Soni, Deepak Gupta, and Gaurav Dubey"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--68", "prompt": "How many authors contributed to 'Meta-Learning: Theory, Algorithms and Applications'?", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "1"}
{"web_name": "ArXiv", "id": "ArXiv--69", "prompt": "What is the DOI of 'Transfer Learning in Natural Language Processing'.", "website": "https://arxiv.org/", "type": "golden", "ans": "10.18653/v1/N19-5004"}